<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Moscow region guide</string>
    <!-- Manors category -->
    <!-- KUskovo -->
    <string name="KName">Kuskovo</string>
    <string name="kDescription"> Kuskovo was one of the first great summer country estates of the
        Russian nobility, and one of the few near Moscow still preserved. Today the estate is the home of the
        Russian State Museum of Ceramics, and the park is a favourite place of recreation for Muscovites.</string>
    <string name="KSite">http://kuskovo.ru/en/</string>
    <string name="KGeo">geo: 55.736947, 37.808537</string>

    <!--Marfino -->
    <string name="MName">Marfino</string>
    <string name="mDescription">Ancient manor Marfino, which is an original monument of Russian architecture
        of the XVIII - XIX centuries, is located near 39 kilometers Dmitrov highway. Famous in its time Palace and Park ensemble,
        magnificent receptions and theatrical performances, the manor Marfino and today is one of the wonderful pages of the history of Russian architecture.</string>
    <string name="mSite">http://marfino.narod.ru/</string>
    <string name="mGeo">geo: 56.080495, 37.563409</string>

    <!--Arkangelskoe -->
    <string name="aName">Arkhangelskoye place</string>
    <string name="aDescription">Arkhangelskoye is a historical estate in Krasnogorsky District, Moscow Oblast, Russia, located around 20 km to the west of Moscow
        and 2 km southwest of Krasnogorsk. The estate is famous for its collection of fine art including paintings, sculptures, furnitures, ceramics and interior.</string>
    <string name="aSite">http://arhangelskoe.su/</string>
    <string name="aGeo">geo: 55.787665, 37.284483</string>

    <!--Serednikovo-->
    <string name="sName">Serednikovo</string>
    <string name="sDescription">Serednikovo is a former estate of Vsevolozhsk and Stolypin, Park and manor ensemble of the
        late XVIII-early XIX century, one of the most famous Lermontov places in Russia.</string>
    <string name="sSite">https://serednikovo.su/</string>
    <string name="sGeo">geo: 55.928713, 37.241219</string>

    <!--other Strings -->
    <string name="Manors">Manors</string>


</resources>
