<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Moscow region guide</string>
    <!-- Manors category -->
    <!-- KUskovo -->
    <string name="KName">Kuskovo</string>
    <string name="kDescription"> Kuskovo was one of the first great summer country estates of the
        Russian nobility, and one of the few near Moscow still preserved. Today the estate is the home of the
        Russian State Museum of Ceramics, and the park is a favourite place of recreation for Muscovites.</string>
    <string name="KSite">http://kuskovo.ru/en/</string>
    <string name="KGeo">geo: 55.736947, 37.808537</string>

    <!--Marfino -->
    <string name="MName">Marfino</string>
    <string name="mDescription">Ancient manor Marfino, which is an original monument of Russian architecture
        of the XVIII - XIX centuries, is located near 39 kilometers Dmitrov highway. Famous in its time Palace and Park ensemble,
        magnificent receptions and theatrical performances, the manor Marfino and today is one of the wonderful pages of the history of Russian architecture.</string>
    <string name="mSite">http://marfino.narod.ru/</string>
    <string name="mGeo">geo: 56.080495, 37.563409</string>

    <!--Arkangelskoe -->
    <string name="aName">Arkhangelskoye place</string>
    <string name="aDescription">Arkhangelskoye is a historical estate in Krasnogorsky District, Moscow Oblast, Russia, located around 20 km to the west of Moscow
        and 2 km southwest of Krasnogorsk. The estate is famous for its collection of fine art including paintings, sculptures, furnitures, ceramics and interior.</string>
    <string name="aSite">http://arhangelskoe.su/</string>
    <string name="aGeo">geo: 55.787665, 37.284483</string>

    <!--Serednikovo-->
    <string name="sName">Serednikovo</string>
    <string name="sDescription">Serednikovo is a former estate of Vsevolozhsk and Stolypin, Park and manor ensemble of the
        late XVIII-early XIX century, one of the most famous Lermontov places in Russia.</string>
    <string name="sSite">https://serednikovo.su/</string>
    <string name="sGeo">geo: 55.928713, 37.241219</string>

    <!--Museums-->
    <!--Bulgakova-->
    <string name="bName">Bulgakov Museum</string>
    <string name="bDescription">The Bulgakov Museum in Moscow is a writer\'s house museum which commemorates the life and work
        of author Mikhail Afanasyevich Bulgakov in an apartment where he lived in Moscow, Russia, and in which he set portions
        of his novel The Master and Margarita. Graffiti, including text from the novel and drawings of its characters,
        have decorated the external walls and stairwells of the apartment building since the beginning of perestroika.</string>
    <string name="bSite">http://bulgakovmuseum.ru/en/visit/</string>
    <string name="bGeo">geo: 55.767207, 37.593735</string>

    <!--State Historical Museum-->
    <string name="hName">State Historical Museum</string>
    <string name="hDesription">The State Historical Museum of Russia is a museum of Russian history wedged between Red Square
        and Manege Square in Moscow. Its exhibitions range from relics of prehistoric tribes that lived on the territory
        of present-day Russia, through priceless artworks acquired by members of the Romanov dynasty. The total number of objects
        in the museum\'s collection comes to millions.</string>
    <string name="hSite">http://en.shm.ru/</string>
    <string name="hGeo">geo: 55.755298, 37.617801</string>

    <!-- State Darwin Museum -->
    <string name="dName">State Darwin Museum</string>
    <string name="dDescription">The State Darwin Museum is a natural history museum in Moscow. The museum was founded in 1907
        by Alexander Kohts (1880-1964) and was the world\'s first museum of evolution explaining the work of Charles Darwin
        as a causal explanation of nature. The museum taxidermist was then Filipp Fedulov.</string>
    <string name="dSite">http://www.darwinmuseum.ru/</string>
    <string name="dGeo">geo: 55.690650, 37.561610</string>

    <!--Museum of the Great Patriotic War -->
    <string name="wName">Museum of the Great Patriotic War</string>
    <string name="wDescription">The Museum of the Great Patriotic War is a history museum located in Moscow at Poklonnaya Gora.
        The building was designed by architect Anatoly Polyansky.Work on the museum began on March 3, 1986, and the museum was
        opened to the public on May 9, 1995.The museum features exhibits and memorials concerning World War II, known in Russia as "The Great Patriotic War".</string>
    <string name="wSite">http://new.victorymuseum.ru/</string>
    <string name="wGeo">geo: 55.730848, 37.504660</string>

    <!--Parks-->
    <!--Gorky Park -->
    <string name="gName">Gorky Park </string>
    <string name="gDescription">Gorky Park, located at Krymsky Val and situated just across the Moskva River from Park Kultury
        Metro station, opened in 1928. The park followed the plan of Konstantin Melnikov, a world-famous Soviet avant-garde and
        constructivist architect, and amalgamated the extensive gardens of the old Golitsyn Hospital and of the Neskuchny Palace,
        covering an area of 300 acres along the river.</string>
    <string name="gSite">http://park-gorkogo.com/</string>
    <string name="gGeo">geo: 55.728338, 37.601193</string>

    <!-- Sparrow Hills -->
    <string name="vName">Sparrow Hills</string>
    <string name="vDescription">Sparrow Hills (Vorobyovy Gory) is a hill on the right bank of the Moskva River and
        one of the highest points in Moscow, reaching a height of 220 m (720 ft), or 60–70 m (200–230 ft) above the river level.
        The observation platform, which gives a good panoramic view of the city, is on a steep bank 85 m (279 ft) above the river,
        or 200 m (660 ft) above sea level. The Luzhniki Stadium , where the opening and closing ceremonies for the 1980 Summer Olympics took place,
        is right below, across the Moskva River. Next to it is the Novodevichy Convent, with its Naryshkin Baroque towers.    </string>
    <string name="vSite">http://mos-holidays.ru/vorobyovy-gory/</string>
    <string name="vGeo">geo: 55.709481, 37.542342</string>

    <!--Izmaylovsky Park -->
    <string name="iName">Izmaylovsky Park</string>
    <string name="iDescription">Izmaylovsky Park is one of the largest parks in Moscow, Russia. Park consists of two areas: Izmaylovsky forest
        and Izmaylovsky park for reacreation. It\'s situated in the Izmaylovo District in the North-East of
        the city. The park was inaugurated in 1931. The northern border of the park is the tram line alongside the Izmailovskaya station
        of the Moscow Metro that serves the park, the southern is the Entuziastov Highway. To the East the park is limited by the Main alley
        and to the West by Electrodny proezd and 1st and 2nd streets of the Izmaylovo menagerie.</string>
    <string name="iSite">http://www.izmailovsky-park.ru/</string>
    <string name="iGeo">geo: 55.772872, 37.753770</string>

    <!-- Sokolniki Park -->
    <string name="soName">Sokolniki Park</string>
    <string name="soDescription">Sokolniki is a typical Russian park, with an aging funfair and other amusements for children, and numerous fast food stalls
        all clustered near the main entrance. In summer the central alleyways are a mass of brightly colored formal flowerbeds, while the depths of the park
        are a wilderness home to pines and spruces, birches and oaks, limes and maples - all trees native to the Moscow region - as well as a number of non-indigenous
        trees, such as larches, cedars, walnut, red oaks, etc. The park\'s wildlife includes hares, squirrels and weasels, as well as 76 types of bird.</string>
    <string name="soSite">http://park.sokolniki.com/</string>
    <string name="soGeo">geo: 55.795137, 37.676410</string>

    <!-- Galleries -->
    <!-- Tretyakov Gallery-->
    <string name="trName">Tretyakov Gallery</string>
    <string name="trDescription">The State Tretyakov Gallery is an art gallery in Moscow, Russia, the foremost depository of Russian fine art in the world. The gallery\'s
        history starts in 1856 when the Moscow merchant Pavel Mikhailovich Tretyakov acquired works by Russian artists of his day with the aim of creating a collection,
        which might later grow into a museum of national art. In 1892, Tretyakov presented his already famous collection of approximately 2,000 works (1,362 paintings,
        526 drawings, and 9 sculptures) to the Russian nation.</string>
    <string name="trSite">https://www.tretyakovgallery.ru/en/</string>
    <string name="trGeo">geo: 55.741433, 37.620700</string>

    <!-- Vinzavod-->
    <string name="vinName">Moscow Contemporary Art Center Winzavod</string>
    <string name="vinDescription">Winzavod is a centre for contemporary arts in Moscow, Russia. Opened in 2007, it is located in a complex of seven industrial buildings from
        the late 19th century including the former brewery (and later winery) called "Moscow Bavaria". Alexander Brodsky is the coordinator of the project.</string>
    <string name="vinSite">http://www.winzavod.ru/eng/</string>
    <string name="vinGeo">geo: 55.755547, 37.664893</string>

    <!-- Gallery of 19th and 20th century European and American Art -->
    <string name="pushName">Gallery of 19th and 20th century European and American Art</string>
    <string name="pushDescription">The Gallery, a new section of the Pushkin State Museum of Fine Arts, opened its doors to the public in August 2006. The Gallery\'s twenty-six
        rooms contain a collection of works by masters of the 19th and 20th centuries. The pride of the Gallery consists of the paintings by French Impressionists and
        Post-Impressionists and masters of the early 20th century: Claude Monet, August Renoir, Alfred Sisley, Camille Pissarro, Edgar Degas, Paul Gauguin, Vincent van Gogh,
        Andre Derain and Menri Rousseau.</string>
    <string name="pushSite">http://www.newpaintart.ru/index.php?lang=en</string>
    <string name="pushGeo">geo: 55.746634, 37.605213</string>

    <!--other Strings -->
    <string name="Manors">Manors</string>
    <string name="Museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="Parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="Galleries">Galleries</string>
    <string name="button">Learn more</string>


</resources>
